这个有约束力，这个很棘手。
Implementing bind, this one is tricky.
这有点棘手，需要了解范围，上下文，调用和应用。
It's a little tricky, you have to know
about scope, and context, call, and apply.
如果你失败了或者你无法得到任何东西
And if you failed on this one or
you couldn't get anything down,
别难过了
don't feel bad.
我们现在要学解决方案了
We're gonna learn the solution now.
学习的最佳部分有时是失败的。
The best part of learning
is sometimes its failure.
你得失败因为你会记得的
You have to fail because you'll remember.
你会记得的因为你就像我花了这么长时间
You'll remember this now because you're
like, I spent so long on this and
然后它就会咔嗒一声，你就会有这个道理。
then it clicks in place,
you're like this makes sense.
这就是 JavaScript 的工作方式。
This is how JavaScript works.
现在我知道更多了
Now I know a little bit more.
说实话我想和那些失败的人合作
And being honest,
I wanna work with people who failed.
我不想和那些只会成功的人一起工作
I don't wanna work with people
who only succeed in life.
这意味着他们没学到什么
That means they didn't learn as much.
并不是说如果你是超级成功的，你没有学到很多东西。
Not saying if you're super successful,
you didn't learn a lot.
但那些失败的人他们知道摔倒的感觉
But people that have failed,
they know what it's like to fall down and
给我回来
get back up.
这就是它的感觉
And that's what it's like.
因为记住你一半的面试都失败了
Because remember,
half the interviews you're gonna fail.
差不多吧你会有一半以上的面试都失败了
Like almost probably, you're gonna fail
over half the interviews you take.
没关系我是说
That's okay.
我失败了很多，我以前在这个问题上失败了。
I failed many,
I failed on this question before.
但现在我知道如何解决这个问题，这只是学习的一部分。
But now I know how to solve it,
and that's just part of learning.
好，我们按标准的方式来处理一个问题，就是，
All right, so let's do the standard way
we always approach a problem, which is,
我需要实现 function.prototype.bind 。
I need to implement
function.prototype.bind.
既然是雏形我就要开始了
Since it's a prototype,
I'm gonna start off there.
因此， function.prototype.bind 。
So function.prototype.bind.
我们知道因为它是我们最终要调用的函数
And we know because it's a function
that we're gonna eventually invoke,
它会成为一个功能
it's gonna be a function.
所以我要说函数
So I'm gonna say function.
现在我要做匿名的工作
And I'm gonna make
an anonymous function for now.
这一功能将会成为一个新的背景
And this function is gonna take
an argument which will be the new context
我们正试图传入
that we're trying to pass in.
我现在就给你打电话
So I'm gonna call you context for now.
我们最终知道我们援引约束的方式是我们正在设定新的环境
And we know eventually the way we invoke
bind is we're setting the new context and
我们待会儿再引用
we're gonna invoke it later.
如果你看到这样的模式或者有人说你正在恢复一个功能
And if you ever see a pattern like this or
someone says, you're returning a function
最终会被调用的你知道它会恢复一个新的功能
that's gonna eventually be invoked later,
you know it's gonna return a new function.
所以，让我们说，返回另一个匿名函数。
So let's say,
return another anonymous function.
我不想再争论这个问题了
And I'm not gonna take any
arguments on this one.
好吧但最终我们要完成什么
Okay, but ultimately,
what do we wanna accomplish with bind?
我们正在尝试返回具有不同上下文的函数。
We're trying to return a function
that has a different context.
我们是如何做到的呢 ?
And how do we do that?
我们的老朋友要么打电话要么申请
We do it with our old
friends either call or apply.
所以我想说这个功能
So I wanna say the function,
我可以说一些函数，然后我想调用或应用它。
I could say some function and
then I wanna call or apply it.
但因为这个有点麻烦
But because this one is
a little trickier and
我可以问一个稍微不同的问题。
I could have asked a slightly
different question.
但我可以说你是怎么做到的
But I could have said,
how do you implement just bind?
这需要一个功能和一个背景。
Which would take a function and a context.
我本可以问的
I could have asked that.
但我想说，这就是现在的雏形。
But I'm saying, this is the prototype now.
所以在这个例子中，我要说，这就是功能本身。
So in this case, so I'm gonna say this,
Is the function itself.
所以我们不需要通过这个功能因为它是隐含在这里的因为我们是
So we don't need to pass in the function
because it's implied in this because we're
在这一功能的雏形上
on the prototype of that function.
好吧我们有了这个功能
Okay, so we have the function.
事实上我要让这更容易
Actually, I'm gonna make
it easier to grock.
我要给你打个电话
I'm gonna call you the function is this.
我需要调用此函数，以便我可以说电话。
And I need to invoke this function so
I can say call.
我将会在此背景下通过。
And I'm going to pass in the context.
就这样了
That's it.
人们点头了，你在家里点头，现在就有道理了。
People are nodding, you're nodding
along at home, it makes sense now.
解决方案很短。
The solution's pretty short.
所以如果我想说如果我不想实施束缚
So if I wanted to say,
if I don't want to just implement bind,
因为我们都有不同的学习方式这是另一种方式
because we all learn differently and
this is a different way of doing it.
退出绑定，它将执行函数和上下文。
Exit bind, it's gonna take a function and
the context.
我可以把它取出来，这个方法也是一样的。
I can just take that out,
and it's the same solution.
好吧有什么问题吗
All right, any questions on this, yes?
>> 我几乎明白，除非我使用的是适用的含义。
&gt;&gt; I almost got it except I used
apply what does apply mean.
>> 是，应用也同样有效。
&gt;&gt; Yes, apply works just as well.
好吧好吧
&gt;&gt; All right, okay.
> > 它会改变方式，而我没有得到更多的进步。
&gt;&gt; It will just change the way,
and I didn't get more advanced.
对我来说这是个完美的解决方案不是完美的解决方案
This to me is a perfect solution or
not a perfect solution, it works for
白板。
white board.
我不是想骗你
I'm not trying to trick you.
如果我想让它变得更困难或者某人是个聪明人
If I wanted to make it more difficult or
someone's being a wise person,
他们是想说我有这个
they're trying to be like, I got this.
我想，好吧，你怎么处理争论呢 ?
I'd be like, okay, so
how do you deal with arguments?
所以你得知道你可以通过电话
So you'd have to know that you can pass or
with call,
这就是这个，电话，我要用的这个说法。
it would be the arguments actually for
this one, for call, I'd use apply.
然后我把它们的论据传播出去。
And then I take the arguments and
I spread them out.
args， arguments，如果我要传递自变量，我就会将它们传播出去。
Args, arguments, and I'd spread them
out if I want to pass arguments.
但我又不想这么深
But, again, I didn't wanna get that deep.
我只想在概念上让人们了解范围和如何
I just wanna know conceptually,
do people understand scope and how to
如果你真的要这么做的话，就会改变它，远远不止是打电话或回复。
change it if you really had to, much
bigger than just calling call or reply.
好吧问题
All right, questions?
>> 我想技术上的问题
&gt;&gt; A more, I guess,
technical question, but
在原型的实施过程中你创造了一个常数
in the implementation of
the prototype you created a constant.
然后你在新的匿名函数中引用了这个常数
And then you referenced that constant in
the new anonymous function that you're
回来了
returning.
那是因为如果你真的用了这个
Is that because if you
actually just used this,
它会被你退回的匿名功能所约束吗
it would be bound to the anonymous
function that you're returning?
> Mm - hm，这就对了。
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm, that's exactly right.
它将绑定到您应用它的复合体。
It would be bound to the complex
that you apply it in.
> > 嗯，好的。
&gt;&gt; Yeah, okay.
>> 但在这种情况下，我们要确保在调用此函数时，
&gt;&gt; But in this case we wanna make sure
that when this function is invoked,
我们要确保这一消息是可以访问的所以我们在范围内声明
we wanna make sure this is accessible,
so we state it within the scope.
问得好
Good question, though.
这就是为什么这个是更先进的
This is why this one's a bit
more advanced, more for
在高级方面，你要了解范围界定之类的。
on the senior side, is you have to
understand scoping and things like that.
好吧如果你再看到这个问题的话
All right, all right,
now if you ever see this question again,
你就会知道一般的结构
you'll know the general structure.
我想如果你得到一般的结构
And I think if you get
the general structure, and
你知道你得打电话或申请点有用的
you realize that you'll have to call or
apply at some point, that's helpful.
但如果你不明白的话
But again, if you didn't get it it's okay.
我们都是从某个地方开始的
We all start somewhere.
我以前都没有回答这些问题。
I have failed all these question before.